From https://www.analog.com/en/products/adxrs450.html#product-overview 
Accessed 11-9-2019

The ADXRS450 is an angular rate sensor (gyroscope) intended for industrial, medical, instrumentation, stabilization, and other high performance applications. An advanced, differential, quad sensor design rejects the influence of linear acceleration, enabling the ADXRS450 to operate in exceedingly harsh environments where shock and vibration are present.

The ADXRS450 uses an internal, continuous self-test archi-tecture. The integrity of the electromechanical system is checked by applying a high frequency electrostatic force to the sense structure to generate a rate signal that can be differentiated from the baseband rate data and internally analyzed.

The ADXRS450 is capable of sensing angular rate of up to ±300°/sec. Angular rate data is presented as a 16-bit word, as part of a 32-bit SPI message.

The ADXRS450 is available in a cavity plastic 16-lead SOIC (SOIC_CAV) and an SMT-compatible vertical mount package (LCC_V), and is capable of operating across both a wide voltage range (3.3 V to 5 V) and temperature range (−40°C to +105°C).


Applications
Rotation sensing medical applications
Rotation sensing industrial and instrumentation
High performance platform stabilization